const blueDeck=[
    
    {question:"stirrup oak her",answer:"strip poker",hint:"naked games"},
    {question:"bud dish hots",answer:"body shots",hint:"belly button"},
    {question:"parr grr all",answer:"bar crawl",hint:"on to the next"},
    {question:"mails drip her",answer:"male stripper",hint:"dollar bills"},
    {question:"hug cup called sure",answer:"hookup culture",hint:"sleeping around"},
    {question:"bod dull hope inner",answer:"bottle opener",hint:"cork"},
    {question:"half dare bar tee",answer:"after party",hint:"round 2"},
    {question:"trunk cog holes",answer:"drunk goggles",hint:"tipsy eyes"},
    {question:"way camp ache",answer:"wake and bake",hint:"off to a good start"},
    {question:"pod pro niece",answer:"pot brownies",hint:"chill chocolate"},
    {question:"diss sicken ate it rif e her",answer:"designated driver",hint:"the real MVP tonight"},
    {question:"ford went he",answer:"420",hint:"national holiday"},
    {question:"pup of as",answer:"puff puff pass",hint:"joint instructions"},
    {question:"may get train",answer:"make it rain",hint:"good weather"},
    {question:"past hutch owe ain't",answer:"pass the joint",hint:"split the pot"},
    {question:"shod game ink appear",answer:"shotgunning a beer",hint:"quick drink"},
    {question:"par dave owl",answer:"party foul",hint:"socially unacceptable"},
    {question:"can ebb hiss",answer:"cannabis",hint:"like MJ"},
    {question:"ha tub ox sing",answer:"hot boxing",hint:"foggy car"},
    {question:"hid tub pong",answer:"hit the bong",hint:"bike toke"},
    {question:"wad herb pong",answer:"water bong",hint:"purified smoke"},
    {question:"read soul oak up",answer:"red solo cup",hint:"beer pong"},
    {question:"jew wool bod",answer:"juulpod",hint:"new cigs"},
    {question:"graph tub here",answer:"craft beer",hint:"not bud light"},
    {question:"spend tub ought all",answer:"spin the bottle",hint:"kiss kiss"},
    {question:"bought til cervix",answer:"bottle service",hint:"grey goose"},
    {question:"due rug tess",answer:"drug test",hint:"pee cup"},
    {question:"fizz dub hum bing",answer:"fist pumping",hint:"clubbing"},
    {question:"moan cheese",answer:"munchies",hint:"hangry"},
    {question:"tech heel huts hot",answer:"tequila shot",hint:"lots of lime"},
    {question:"read bow fog caw",answer:"redbull vodka",hint:"classic combo"},
    {question:"score be on pole",answer:"scorpion bowl",hint:"group drink"},
    {question:"pod tum mull his minnows us",answer:"bottomless mimosas",hint:"brunch"},
    {question:"drub bet lie kits sot",answer:"drop it like its hot",hint:"snooooop"},
    {question:"napper half fie heifer",answer:"never have i ever",hint:"secrets told"},
    {question:"ball hack doubt",answer:"blacked out",hint:"drunken darkness"},
    {question:"cram pear heave ought caw",answer:"cranberry vodka",hint:"spiked juice"},
    {question:"tab pith hug egg",answer:"tap the egg",hint:"pour the beer"},
    {question:"pinch shrink gang",answer:"binge drinking",hint:"dedicated hydration"},
    {question:"barrel limp picks",answer:"beer olympics",hint:"local competition"},
    {question:"furl oak hoe",answer:"four loko",hint:"banned substance"},
    {question:"far tin gimp up lick",answer:"farting in public",hint:"noisy outside"},
    {question:"bogs due i’m",answer:"boxed wine",hint:"franzia"},
    {question:"hank oaf irk your",answer:"hangover cure",hint:"sunday medication"},
    {question:"paw where our",answer:"power hour",hint:"beer timer"},
    {question:"sog key pom",answer:"sake bomb",hint:"beer cocktail"},
    {question:"jane’s moat king",answer:"chain smoking",hint:"lotta butts"},
    {question:"fay guy tee",answer:"fake id",hint:"golden ticket"},
    {question:"bob ping bought tolls",answer:"popping bottles",hint:"champagne"},
    {question:"app he yeah war",answer:"happy hour",hint:"joyous time"},
    {question:"pain yuck hole odd huh",answer:"pina colada",hint:"pineapple punch"},
    {question:"dirt rugged heel her",answer:"drug dealer",hint:"weed"},
    {question:"thor tier hack",answer:"30 rack",hint:"bud light"},
    {question:"saws itch barred hay",answer:"sausage party",hint:"all male"},
    {question:"dare team art teenie",answer:"dirty martini",hint:"not clean"},
    {question:"zig are wet",answer:"cigarette",hint:"juul"},
    {question:"peer belle he",answer:"beer belly",hint:"too much bud"},
    {question:"mark car eat duh",answer:"margarita",hint:"salty rim"},
    {question:"room manned coat",answer:"rum and coke",hint:"classic combo"},
    {question:"shale low shods",answer:"jello shots",hint:"dessert drink"},
    {question:"prow nowed",answer:"brown out",hint:"one too many"},
    {question:"raw link babe hair",answer:"rolling paper",hint:"green accessory"},
    {question:"tea ages he",answer:"thc",hint:"hippie chemistry"},
    {question:"kay gust and",answer:"keg stand",hint:"tap it"},
    {question:"foal hip cub",answer:"flip cup",hint:"red solo"},
    {question:"hog tote bear vest",answer:"oktoberfest",hint:"bier"},
    {question:"gin dairy feel barred tee",answer:"gender reveal party",hint:"pink or blue"},
    {question:"trunk eggs stink",answer:"drunk texting",hint:"idk where i am"},
    {question:"seep peed he wile",answer:"cbd oil",hint:"for anxiety"},
    {question:"past hutch owe ain’t",answer:"pass the joint",hint:"split the pot"},
    
    {question:"shod gone ink appear",answer:"shotgunning a beer",hint:"quick drink"}
    ];
    const yellowDeck=[
    
        {question:"fit he sheds off cray",answer:"fifty shades of grey",hint:"whips and chain"},  {question:"core run teen",answer:"quarantine",hint:"'rona"},
     {question:"cuh rone ahvi rust",answer:"corona virus",hint:"'rona"},
     {question:"suhw ayp reyt",answer:"swipe right",hint:"’she/hes hottt"},
        {question:"fog chair he",answer:"fuckjerry",hint:"meme account"},
        {question:"guy leech hen her",answer:"kylie jenner",hint:"makeup"},
        {question:"trick her worn in",answer:"trigger warning",hint:"alert"},
        {question:"crap temp eye tub pushy",answer:"grab them by the pussy",hint:"trump advice"},
        {question:"nun she ammo",answer:"non gmo",hint:"nutrition"},
        {question:"hatch meows hide hobo dad",answer:"catch me outside how about that",hint:"dr. phil"},
        {question:"fish hits bin hers",answer:"fidget spinners",hint:"rotating distraction"},
        {question:"hue own lee leaf ones",answer:"you only live once",hint:"limited existence"},
        {question:"day yam tan knee hole",answer:"damn daniel",hint:"white vans"},
        {question:"knit flick sand shill",answer:"netflix and chill",hint:"watching movies"},
        {question:"sad hurt ace surf forth a voice",answer:"saturdays are for the boys",hint:"barstool sports"},
        {question:"chut ches lied",answer:"cha cha slide",hint:"wedding moves"},
        {question:"their heels limp shed he",answer:"the real slim shady",hint:"eminem"},
        {question:"sid hop drying tomb ache kvetch have been",answer:"stop trying to make fetch happen",hint:"regina george"},
        {question:"own wind stays weave hair ping",answer:"on wednesdays, we wear pink",hint:"weekly color preference"},
        {question:"hid sprint heap itch",answer:"its britney bitch",hint:"oops! I did it again"},
        {question:"veer off mess sing oat",answer:"fear of missing out",hint:"social anxiety"},
        {question:"this drug gull israel",answer:"the struggle is real",hint:"first world problems"},
        {question:"hint turn ed rolls",answer:"internet trolls",hint:"online bullies"},
        {question:"real agents sip gulls",answer:"relationship goals",hint:"power couple"},
        {question:"hike ant eve hen",answer:"i cant even",hint:"ugh, whatever"},
        {question:"per rake tee inner ned",answer:"break the internet",hint:"crash the web"},
        {question:"boy full leash awe",answer:"bye felicia",hint:"adios, amiga"},
        {question:"hey dares con a hayed",answer:"haters gonna hate",hint:"critics criticize"},
        {question:"hay knob putty god dime fourth hat",answer:"aint nobody got time for that",hint:"i got bronchitis"},
        {question:"tad swat cheese head",answer:"thats what she said",hint:"classic response"},
        {question:"razzled ding pitch vase",answer:"resting bitch face",hint:"lingering facial rage"},
        {question:"fifed holler food lawn",answer:"5 dollar footlong",hint:"eat fresh"},
        {question:"hints tug rams hole leper hid tea",answer:"instagram celebrity",hint:"internet famous"},
        {question:"dez pus seed hoe",answer:"despacito",hint:"taquito, dorito"},
        {question:"ham a sauna let’s uh",answer:"amazon alexa",hint:"robot commands"},
        {question:"stir range earth inks",answer:"stranger things",hint:"upside down"},
        {question:"came off drones",answer:"game of thrones",hint:"iron throne"},
        {question:"brute teen pout her",answer:"protein powder",hint:"strong sugar"},
        {question:"sun nap chad’s door he",answer:"snapchat story",hint:"24-hour special"},
        {question:"hints toe cram starry",answer:"instagram story",hint:"no filter"},
        {question:"hud yolk uh",answer:"hot yoga",hint:"warm stretching"},
        {question:"hoop purr pull",answer:"uber pool",hint:"shared ride"},
        {question:"tethers diss rail",answer:"the thirst is real",hint:"parched"},
        {question:"bull lag fried hay",answer:"black friday",hint:"crazy shopping"},
        {question:"aight hook uphill henna bees uh",answer:"i took a pill in ibiza",hint:"mike posner"},
        {question:"sure gore furry",answer:"sugar free",hint:"boring alternative"},
        {question:"glide much henge",answer:"climate change",hint:"carbon crisis"},
        {question:"cause mob hole lid in",answer:"cosmopolitan",hint:"drink and mag"},
        {question:"king cord ash yen whizzed",answer:"kim kardashian west",hint:"keeping up"},
        {question:"mic cup two door real",answer:"makeup tutorial",hint:"beauty 101"},
        {question:"tint hurt eight",answer:"tinder date",hint:"it’s a match"},
        {question:"purr roam hands",answer:"bromance",hint:"i love you, man"},
        {question:"bell who awful",answer:"blue waffle",hint:"fake STD"},
        {question:"wear caw haul leg",answer:"workaholic",hint:"job addicted"},
        {question:"freak when doff liar my holes",answer:"frequent flyer miles",hint:"united airlines"},
        {question:"huh verb oar duh",answer:"hoverboard",hint:"scooter"},
        {question:"prix aunt kush hoe bra",answer:"priyanka chopra",hint:"bollywood"},
        {question:"sate donut spur aid hit",answer:"say it dont spray it",hint:"saliva"},
        {question:"glow eek hard ashy am",answer:"khloe kardashian",hint:"keeping up"},
        {question:"vector hero yell",answer:"victory royale",hint:"fortnite"},
        {question:"ton hold romp shoe near",answer:"donald trump jr",hint:"son of a"},
        {question:"mime elks ache brim saul dubai’s tooth uh yod",answer:"my milkshake brings all the boys to the yard",hint:"booty shake"},
        {question:"huge act mend",answer:"hugh jackman",hint:"wolverine"},
        {question:"why and ran holds",answer:"ryan reynolds",hint:"actor"},
        {question:"bay beam on uh",answer:"baby mama",hint:"parent"},
        {question:"debt tub bool",answer:"deadpool",hint:"superhero"},
        {question:"tech a gel pal",answer:"take a chill pill",hint:"overreacting"},
        {question:"star mead annuals",answer:"stormy daniels",hint:"bad weather"},
        {question:"foot comb uh",answer:"food coma",hint:"thanksgiving"},
        {question:"fenced a hug hound",answer:"finsta account",hint:"second profile"},
        {question:"tech get mads tear",answer:"ticketmaster",hint:"event boss"},
        {question:"yeah skew ween",answer:"yas queen",hint:"you go girl"},
        {question:"knew foam hood is",answer:"new phone who dis",hint:"no contacts"},
        {question:"croupe miss itch",answer:"group message",hint:"text us"},
        {question:"furry wife eye",answer:"free wifi",hint:"starbucks"},
        {question:"stuff fin cure ray",answer:"stephen curry",hint:"MVP"},
        {question:"iowa cope lie hiss",answer:"i woke up like this",hint:"flawless"},
        {question:"soak wad coals",answer:"squad goals",hint:"cool kids"},
        {question:"gash shole knee",answer:"cash only",hint:"ATM"},
        {question:"for tea your all diversion",answer:"40 year old virgin",hint:"steve carell"},
        {question:"had meow null ink den",answer:"add me on linkedin",hint:"networking"},
        {question:"jews cull lens",answer:"juice cleanse",hint:"liquid health"},
        {question:"of venture sin fin it you oar",answer:"avengers infinite war",hint:"thanos"},
        {question:"whole avant form wrist mist issue",answer:"all i want for christmas is you",hint:"mariah"},
        {question:"furry dude aid chip ping",answer:"free 2 day shipping",hint:"prime target"},
        {question:"hue nick horn fir rap bush sheen owe",answer:"unicorn frappuccino",hint:"magical drink"},
        {question:"broke he monk hoe",answer:"pokemon go",hint:"pikachu"},
        {question:"stir hate owe dug humped in",answer:"straight outta compton",hint:"ice cube"},
        {question:"clue tin furry",answer:"gluten free",hint:"fake bread"},
        {question:"died botch ill hinge",answer:"tide pod challenge",hint:"eating soap"},
        {question:"mocks suck curb berk",answer:"mark zuckerberg",hint:"news feed"},
        {question:"sue why bride",answer:"swipe right",hint:"it’s a match"},
        {question:"set ton owe won heifer",answer:"said no one ever",hint:"snarky reply"},
        {question:"key bit won hunt rid",answer:"keep it 100",hint:"the real deal"},
        {question:"pitch pull ease",answer:"bitch please!",hint:"finger snap"},
        {question:"tour king",answer:"twerking",hint:"modern shake"},
        {question:"aim his own burr rhyme",answer:"amazon prime",hint:"bezos"},
        {question:"walk hun dove oar ev her",answer:"wakanda forever",hint:"east africa"},
        {question:"fur stew hurled prop plums",answer:"first world problems",hint:"not real issues"},
        {question:"comp hooch ya",answer:"kombucha",hint:"drink fad"},
        {question:"birch who’ll ray yell lid he",answer:"virtual reality",hint:"fake life"},
        {question:"sun nab shat filled her",answer:"snapchat filter",hint:"virtual makeup"},
        {question:"van heap hack",answer:"fanny pack",hint:"strap-on fashion"},
        {question:"bore dare well",answer:"border wall",hint:"trump’s fence"},
        {question:"shelf dry fink curse",answer:"self driving cars",hint:"robo wheels"},
        {question:"that he itch use",answer:"daddy issues",hint:"father probs"},
        {question:"ran shore blush ease",answer:"ranch or blue cheese?",hint:"buffalo wings"},
        {question:"two huey fen lived pro",answer:"do you even lift bro?",hint:"gym membership"},
        {question:"quack his sex draw",answer:"guac is extra",hint:"chipotle"},
        {question:"mayan knock honda toned",answer:"my anaconda don’t",hint:"nicki"},
        {question:"aims heck see hand eye note",answer:"i’m sexy and i know it",hint:"hot and confident"},
        {question:"burn niece handlers",answer:"bernie sanders",hint:"universal healthcare"},
        {question:"pressed feet tin",answer:"breast feeding",hint:"milk"},
        {question:"yen if hearse sale elf kay her",answer:"universal healthcare",hint:"total support"},
        {question:"crib took her rinse see",answer:"cryptocurrency",hint:"fake moola"},
        {question:"boo pay moat she",answer:"poop emoji",hint:"smelly smile"},
        {question:"slight tint huey ore tea hems",answer:"slide into your dms",hint:"pickup line"},
        {question:"vague noose",answer:"fake news",hint:"legit info"},
        {question:"ellen mayo",answer:"lmao",hint:"cracking up"},
        {question:"foe dope bum",answer:"photobomb",hint:"exploding image"},
        {question:"call ick bayed",answer:"clickbait",hint:"headliner"},
        {question:"womb hank rush when stay",answer:"women crush wednesday",hint:"hump day"},
        {question:"mank rush moaned hay",answer:"man crush monday",hint:"weekly bf post"},
        {question:"go shell law",answer:"coachella",hint:"getting festive"},
        {question:"pars duels boards",answer:"barstool sports",hint:"boston blog"},
        {question:"huff fog autoed host",answer:"avocado toast",hint:"best breakfast"},
        {question:"check hen nan due awfuls",answer:"chicken and waffles",hint:"soul food"},
        {question:"bump ken spies slot day",answer:"pumpkin spice latte",hint:"basic caffeine"},
        {question:"hids nod hue wets may",answer:"its not you its me",hint:"breakup"},
        {question:"thorough winks aid",answer:"throwing shade",hint:"tossing insults"},
        {question:"bush rop raw",answer:"push up bra",hint:" lifted"},
        {question:"mere ores elf fee",answer:"mirror selfie",hint:"reflection"},
        {question:"sore hay nods ore hee",answer:"sorry not sorry",hint:"no apology"},
        {question:"buffers toll led meat ache us elf fee",answer:"but first let me take a selfie",hint:"wait snap a pic"},
        {question:"whirls tar rip pop",answer:"worldstar hiphop",hint:"fight videos"},
        {question:"bays sig up hitch",answer:"basic bitch",hint:"standard human"},
        {question:"duke earls swung up",answer:"two girls one cup",hint:"shit you can’t unsee"},
        {question:"beep perve favor",answer:"bieber fever",hint:"canadian sickness"},
        {question:"cough inks ease in",answer:"cuffing season",hint:"wintertime"},
        {question:"shake fur rum stayed of harm",answer:"jake from state farm",hint:"khaki model"},
        {question:"a dull thing",answer:"adulting",hint:"grown-up"},
        {question:"car mush up itch",answer:"karmas a bitch",hint:"cause and effect"},
        {question:"starred if rum tub pot hum",answer:"started from the bottom",hint:"no privilege"},
        {question:"stalk hint of rends own",answer:"stuck in the friend zone",hint:"high five!"},
        {question:"thor dwee link",answer:"third wheeling",hint:"here for support"},
        {question:"dean mage purr wreck nun see",answer:"teenage pregnancy",hint:"young momma"},
        {question:"fun dizzy food pall",answer:"fantasy football",hint:"gambling"},
        {question:"pow hurk up pull",answer:"power couple",hint:"perfect pair"},
        {question:"sups cur ripe tomb eye sham null",answer:"subscribe to my channel",hint:"youtube"},
        {question:"jenner agency",answer:"generation z",hint:"up-and-coming"},
        {question:"cape gall manned care ray han",answer:"keep calm and carry on",hint:"poster"},
        {question:"fret shim in fit teen",answer:"freshman fifteen",hint:"collegiate perks"},
        {question:"ma shawl hot hey",answer:"matcha latte",hint:"new drink fad"},
        {question:"purry war cowed",answer:"pre workout",hint:"before lifting"},
        {question:"cell fees tick",answer:"selfie stick",hint:"photo assistant"},
        {question:"egg straw hay elf",answer:"extra af",hint:"so additional"},
        {question:"enter net vain muss",answer:"internet famous",hint:"known online"},
        {question:"sums how’d gums shout",answer:"suns out guns out",hint:"tank top"},
        {question:"shy hold dish camp he no",answer:"childish gambino",hint:"rapper"},
        {question:"ump hate hint urn zip",answer:"unpaid internship",hint:"college student"},
        {question:"the row pack thirst hay",answer:"throwback thursday",hint:"weekly memz"},
        {question:"cape in cup width hug hard ashy ins",answer:"keeping up with the kardashians",hint:"guilty pleasure"},
        {question:"wet thing seize hen",answer:"wedding season",hint:"promising series"},
        {question:"ike hot if rum mime hum uh",answer:"i got it from my momma",hint:"in my DNA"},
        {question:"odd doe core egged",answer:"autocorrect",hint:"text replacement"},
        {question:"bin joe wad shin",answer:"binge watching",hint:"tv marathon"},
        {question:"lung air toned gayer",answer:"long hair dont care",hint:"lovely locks"},
        {question:"can mold oh",answer:"camel toe",hint:"sahara foot"},
        {question:"sill lab hiss wake",answer:"syllabus week",hint:"new semester"},
        {question:"ron men newt holes",answer:"ramen noodles",hint:"american delicacy"},
        {question:"fife oak log chad hoe",answer:"five oclock shadow",hint:"short stubble"},
        {question:"pie juan kit won furry",answer:"buy 1 get 1 free",hint:"gmail promotion"},
        {question:"dime sinew roam men",answer:"times new roman",hint:"MLA format"},
        {question:"moor nim bur wrath",answer:"morning breath",hint:"wake-up smell"},
        {question:"snap bowl fax",answer:"snapple facts",hint:"liquid knowledge"},
        {question:"chest who wit",answer:"just do it",hint:"global slogan"},
        {question:"her pinned ick shun hairy",answer:"urban dictionary",hint:"fun meanings"},
        {question:"food cub hitches skit moan hay",answer:"fuck bitches get money",hint:"ignorant motto"},
        {question:"race sore perm",answer:"razor burn",hint:"shaving sucks"},
        {question:"hid scum plug hated",answer:"its complicated",hint:"relationship status"},
        {question:"lib full half all of",answer:"live laugh love",hint:"another poster quote"},
        {question:"dome hutch chin firm hey shun",answer:"too much information",hint:"but why"},
        {question:"a dent chum hoe were",answer:"attention whore",hint:"fame obsessed"},
        {question:"hope in real asian ship",answer:"open relationship",hint:"extramarital"},
        {question:"carp pull carry oak he",answer:"carpool karaoke",hint:"sing-along"},
        {question:"heir being bee",answer:"airbnb",hint:"couch surfing"},
        {question:"wind her ritz cum ink",answer:"winter is coming",hint:"snow"},
        {question:"tub hatch chill or wet",answer:"the bachelorette",hint:"love olympics"},
        {question:"kin trick loam are",answer:"kendrick lamar",hint:"DAMN."},
        {question:"shams there ab her",answer:"chance the rapper",hint:"probability"},
        {question:"neck key men notch",answer:"nicki minaj",hint:"anaconda"},
        {question:"cart he pea",answer:"cardi b",hint:"okurrrr"},
        {question:"gone yay whizzed",answer:"kanye west",hint:"genius"},
        {question:"dutch aims mole curse",answer:"the chainsmokers",hint:"cigarettes"},
        {question:"duh hammed mate stale",answer:"the handmaids tale",hint:"hulu"},
        {question:"if hung cut romp",answer:"ivanka trump",hint:"#1 daughter"},
        {question:"he’ll lawn mosque",answer:"elon musk",hint:"iron man"},
        {question:"hum pull bore rag",answer:"humble brag",hint:"sneaky ego"},
        {question:"phase bucks tall king",answer:"facebook stalking",hint:"social spy"},
        {question:"trains form agent who’s stay",answer:"transformation tuesday",hint:"insta ritual"},
        {question:"ham ions peak her",answer:"am i on speaker",hint:"loud phone"},
        {question:"wads thaw why vibe ass sword",answer:"what’s the wifi password",hint:"saving data"},
        {question:"bay purse draws",answer:"paper straws",hint:"eco-friendly"},
        {question:"whip stone dull hi",answer:"hips don’t lie",hint:"shakira"},
        {question:"low roll or yam knee",answer:"laurel or yanny",hint:"listen close"},
        {question:"son dane knived vote bowl",answer:"sunday night football",hint:"wings and pizza"},
        {question:"sit orange his alm oats fool",answer:"storage is almost full",hint:"need memory"},
        {question:"reed seating air lime",answer:"receding hairline",hint:"growing forehead"},
        {question:"cub hulls mesh hutch",answer:"couples massage",hint:"all the feels"},
        {question:"burr thick hunt roll",answer:"birth control",hint:"sexual safety"},
        {question:"red ray seeds",answer:"read receipts",hint:"imessage"},
        {question:"yolk hub ants",answer:"yoga pants",hint:"tight and comfy"},
        {question:"are he amuck ran day",answer:"ariana grande",hint:"ponytail"},
        {question:"shone ham knit tee",answer:"sean hannity",hint:"foxy"},
        {question:"men him hum owe age",answer:"minimum wage",hint:"per hour"},
        {question:"hoop heard rife fair",answer:"uber driver",hint:"5 stars"},
        {question:"pray kink how’d",answer:"breaking out",hint:"puberty"},
        {question:"eel lips sob bath wear in",answer:"elizabeth warren",hint:"native american"},
        {question:"gunk on troll",answer:"gun control",hint:"amendment"},
        {question:"brick gnat seed hest",answer:"pregnancy test",hint:"plus or minus"},
        {question:"eggs plows if dire hey ya",answer:"explosive diarrhea",hint:"boom toilet"},
        {question:"eggs pox sole i’ve",answer:"xbox live",hint:"video game"},
        {question:"fork hop as whirred",answer:"forgot password",hint:"username"},
        {question:"bore he’d dope pole",answer:"burrito bowl",hint:"chipotle"},
        {question:"ink hog knead ode",answer:"incognito mode",hint:"secret search"},
        {question:"far rat turn it heap rod her",answer:"fraternity brother",hint:"greekish"},
        {question:"full hi yank sole low",answer:"flying solo",hint:"free like a bird"},
        {question:"hen newest fill led dale fear porn hand raced",answer:"in west philadelphia born and raised",hint:"bel air"},
        {question:"stood den dead",answer:"student debt",hint:"so college"},
        {question:"calf itched",answer:"catfished",hint:"fake ID"},
        {question:"meh come air ick auger rate akin",answer:"make america great again",hint:"on a red hat"},
        {question:"hill loom men hottie",answer:"illuminati",hint:"beyonce"},
        {question:"shin me fail on",answer:"jimmy fallon",hint:"late night"},
        {question:"awed toad dune",answer:"autotune",hint:"t-pain"},
        {question:"lint seal owe hand",answer:"lindsay lohan",hint:"parent trap"},
        {question:"lug would chew mate made who",answer:"look what you made me do",hint:"swift"},
        {question:"brr had leak hoop her",answer:"bradley cooper",hint:"a star is born"},
        {question:"torn town furrow hut",answer:"turn down for what",hint:"lil jon"},
        {question:"hone limed agree",answer:"online degree",hint:"phoenix"},
        {question:"fifes heck gunned roll",answer:"five second rule",hint:"safe to eat"},
        {question:"check full hay",answer:"chick fil a",hint:"christian food"},
        {question:"coal ledge job how’d",answer:"college dropout",hint:"zuckerberg"},
        {question:"bus so feat",answer:"buzzfeed",hint:"online quiz"},
        {question:"eighty age tee",answer:"adhd",hint:"can’t sit still"},
        {question:"we’re duh flax bud oak hay",answer:"weird flex but ok",hint:"show off"},
        {question:"beer purr retch her",answer:"peer pressure",hint:"c’mon, do it"},
        {question:"fair if i’d hook hound",answer:"verified account",hint:"blue check mark"},
        {question:"hints stuck ramp gap shin",answer:"instagram caption",hint:"subtitle"},
        {question:"son herb pod",answer:"summer bod",hint:"six pack"},
        {question:"phase poke off his shoal",answer:"facebook official",hint:"in a relationship"},
        {question:"burrows pea four rose",answer:"bros before hoes",hint:"fratty motto"},
        {question:"coal brook off he",answer:"cold brew coffee",hint:"icy caffeine"},
        {question:"pig sore hit tint tap open",answer:"pics or it didnt happen",hint:"picture proof"},
        {question:"haze sear ray",answer:"hey siri",hint:"personal assistant"},
        {question:"pole lid tick glee anchor wrecked",answer:"politically incorrect",hint:"offensive"},
        {question:"hall moan dumb elk",answer:"almond milk",hint:"nutty drink"},
        {question:"shoals hike hole",answer:"soulcycle",hint:"bike club"},
        {question:"heart fish hole and hell itch hens",answer:"artificial intelligence",hint:"fake smart"},
        {question:"herb pam how’d tvet hers",answer:"urban outfitters",hint:"cool clothes"},
        {question:"ab pole moose sick",answer:"apple music",hint:"fruit tunes"},
        {question:"shone meant diss",answer:"shawn mendes",hint:"in my blood"},
        {question:"pose dumb alone",answer:"post malone",hint:"face tats"},
        {question:"meat whom hoove mint",answer:"me too movement",hint:"time’s up"},
        {question:"sack jewel lorry hen day chin",answer:"sexual orientation",hint:"born this way"},
        {question:"hay thee yes sim",answer:"atheism",hint:"ungodly"},
        {question:"pot turn knit teed hest",answer:"paternity test",hint:"maury"},
        {question:"rush a knack king",answer:"russian hacking",hint:"interference"},
        {question:"fray dome muffs beach",answer:"freedom of speech",hint:"say whatcha want"},
        {question:"sigh burp pully inn",answer:"cyber bullying",hint:"virtual villain"},
        {question:"ache quill bay",answer:"equal pay",hint:"every dollar counts"},
        {question:"calf finned her ant",answer:"kevin durant",hint:"top baller"},
        {question:"low camp haul",answer:"logan paul",hint:"social media star"},
        {question:"press hid hinder ump",answer:"president trump",hint:"orange face"},
        {question:"jim tam lawn tree",answer:"gym tan laundry",hint:"jersey shore"},
        {question:"rope herd mule lore",answer:"robert mueller",hint:"special detective"},
        {question:"kin chaw noon",answer:"kim jong un",hint:"rocket man"},
        {question:"kin you’ve hem mow mi",answer:"can you venmo me",hint:"split the bill"},
        {question:"vie her vest if all",answer:"fyre festival",hint:"fake event"},
        {question:"snake her reds",answer:"sneakerheads",hint:"new shoes"},
        {question:"him pea chum mint",answer:"impeachment",hint:"goodbye trump"}
        
    ]
    
    
    
    const redDeck=[
       
    {question:"digs a king libs",answer:"dick sucking",hint:"orally gifted"},
    {question:"bra silly anne whacks",answer:"brazilian wax",hint:"beach trimming"},
    {question:"hid thud she’s pot",answer:"hit the g spot",hint:"bull’s eye"},
    {question:"lab bud ants",answer:"lap dance",hint:"paid ride"},
    {question:"rivers scowl curl",answer:"reverse cowgirl",hint:"backward rider"},
    {question:"tub bullpen hid race sun",answer:"double penetration",hint:"extra stuffed"},
    {question:"cold hen chow hair",answer:"golden shower",hint:"urinating hygiene"},
    {question:"bud pull lug",answer:"butt plug",hint:"clog the hole"},
    {question:"say foe herd",answer:"safe word",hint:"backup plan"},
    {question:"duh heep their oat",answer:"deep throat",hint:"all in"},
    {question:"toggled hurt heat whom he",answer:"talk dirty to me",hint:"naughty language"},
    {question:"call it tour his",answer:"clitoris",hint:"sex organ"},
    {question:"six zoo wing",answer:"sex wing",hint:"playground toy"},
    {question:"men nog gummy",answer:"monogamy",hint:"locked down"},
    {question:"though wok calves aim",answer:"the walk of shame",hint:"morning-after stroll"},
    {question:"cop bull logged",answer:"cockblocked",hint:"unwanted defense"},
    {question:"dig beer zing",answer:"dick piercing",hint:"sausage ring"},
    {question:"offer dub ant sand chop",answer:"over the pants hand job",hint:"heavy-duty rub"},
    {question:"in flay doubles hex tall",answer:"inflatable sex doll",hint:"blow-up partner"},
    {question:"loop reek hand",answer:"lubricant",hint:"slippery"},
    {question:"his cat tin ought inner ear",answer:"its getting hot in here",hint:"nelly"},
    {question:"heated tank wit id",answer:"hit it and quit it",hint:"one time"},
    {question:"four neg age in",answer:"fornication",hint:"under the covers"},
    {question:"keg reef flux",answer:"gag reflex",hint:"taking it all in"},
    {question:"dig kin hub ox",answer:"dick in a box",hint:"boxed sausage"},
    {question:"ore holes eggs",answer:"sex oral",hint:"going down"},
    {question:"bud make it",answer:"butt naked",hint:"nice buns"},
    {question:"sack son deb each",answer:"sex on the beach",hint:"fun in the sun"},
    {question:"sin goal lander head eat who mink goal",answer:"single and ready to mingle",hint:"flying solo"},
    {question:"trees hum",answer:"threesome",hint:"kinky trio"},
    {question:"bop login draw pit",answer:"pop lock and drop it",hint:"dance it"},
    {question:"cut dull putty",answer:"cuddle buddy",hint:"snuggling"},
    {question:"fur rents switch pen of its",answer:"friends with benefits",hint:"keeping it casual"},
    {question:"fairy kin tush eats",answer:"freak in the sheets",hint:"kinky underwear"},
    {question:"deep hag king",answer:"tea bagging",hint:"not coffee"},
    {question:"he’d check you’ll hay shin",answer:"ejaculation",hint:"milky discharge"},
    {question:"pour bot hem",answer:"power bottom",hint:"lower strength"},
    {question:"bay or bags hex",answer:"bareback sex",hint:"unprotected"},
    {question:"glow ray hull",answer:"glory hole",hint:"anonymous pleasure"},
    {question:"zoo wing or potty",answer:"swinger party",hint:"orgy hangout"},
    {question:"sex sigh hold",answer:"sexiled",hint:"kicked out"},
    {question:"calm heed at tea",answer:"call me daddy",hint:"labeled father"},
    {question:"drow gin gone dumbs",answer:"trojan condoms",hint:"rubbers"},
    {question:"den hinged hill though",answer:"10 inch dildo",hint:"lengthy load"},
    {question:"lay sunder weigh her",answer:"lace underwear",hint:"cheeky panties"},
    {question:"aim null zoo thing shell",answer:"anal soothing gel",hint:"tushy blue"},
    {question:"full less shell lied",answer:"fleshlight",hint:"male masturbator"},
    {question:"sir cull shirk",answer:"circle jerk",hint:"helping hands"},
    {question:"six dang",answer:"sexting",hint:"snapchat"},
    {question:"muh knees hot",answer:"money shot",hint:"booming dollar"},
    {question:"din call parry",answer:"dingleberry",hint:"hairy problem"},
    {question:"heck plan team owe gee",answer:"eggplant emoji",hint:"not a vegetable"},
    {question:"pea gym mow she",answer:"peach emoji",hint:"animated butt"},
    {question:"high juan shoe-ins height off may",answer:"i want you inside of me",hint:"polite request"},
    {question:"bore knock rough he",answer:"pornography",hint:"incognito window"},
    {question:"high lie kit her of",answer:"i like it rough",hint:"masochism"},
    {question:"stirp hip purple",answer:"stripper pole",hint:"metallic tool"},
    {question:"chad drool hat",answer:"chatroulette",hint:"random strangers"},
    {question:"aim hole beets",answer:"anal beads",hint:"booty jewelry"},
    {question:"sent ink newts",answer:"sending nudes",hint:"photo text"},
    {question:"show dub pant kids meh",answer:"shut up and kiss me",hint:"quiet makeout"},
    {question:"sped doors wall hoe",answer:"spit or swallow",hint:"BJ thoughts"},
    {question:"mourn hang would",answer:"morning wood",hint:"sunrise surprise"},
    {question:"shook herd addie",answer:"sugar daddy",hint:"sweet father"},
    {question:"purry match hurry shack yule asian",answer:"premature ejaculation",hint:"too soon"},
    {question:"pick tick kin hurt she",answer:"big dick energy",hint:"cocky"},
    {question:"pants eggs shoe well",answer:"pansexual",hint:"all on the table"},
    {question:"hay reap you bus",answer:"hairy pubes",hint:"jungle down under"},
    {question:"book hockey",answer:"bukkake",hint:"group effort"},
    {question:"don’t hoof hug",answer:"down to fuck",hint:"yes/no question"},
    {question:"for wren shuck his sing",answer:"french kissing",hint:"eiffel tower"},
    {question:"hey null fish ding",answer:"anal fisting",hint:"high give in the back"},
    {question:"who ed reams",answer:"wet dreams",hint:"slippery sleep"},
    {question:"sicks teen hine",answer:"69",hint:"team work"},
    {question:"miss shun hairy boss itch shun",answer:"missionary position",hint:"starter pose"},
    {question:"sid ton knife ace",answer:"sit on my face",hint:"vip seats"},
    {question:"fay club oops",answer:"fake boobs",hint:"plastic"},
    {question:"nom pen hit rate ifs eggs",answer:"non penetrative sex",hint:"outercourse"},
    {question:"as tomb out",answer:"ass to mouth",hint:"taste of booty"},
    {question:"orc gasp him",answer:"orgasm",hint:"pleasant finish"},
    {question:"hiss sit tinny it",answer:"is it in yet",hint:"tiny tim"},
    {question:"poll lick come me",answer:"polygamy",hint:"free bird"},
    {question:"ear reptile this funk sheen",answer:"erectile dysfunction",hint:"get up plz"},
    {question:"try yum bing",answer:"dry humping",hint:"clothed sex"},
    {question:"hey rig runt tell",answer:"hair grundle",hint:"jungle butt"},
    {question:"food fed dish",answer:"foot fetish",hint:"tasty toes"},
    {question:"tom mean hay tricks",answer:"dominatrix",hint:"naughty boss"},
    {question:"sit drab pond hill though",answer:"strap on dildo",hint:"sexcessory"},
    {question:"nib pull peers sing",answer:"nipple piercing",hint:"body jewel"},
    {question:"chow wears hex",answer:"shower sex",hint:"waterfall"},
    {question:"unhides tanned",answer:"one night stand",hint:"in and out"},
    {question:"spur mud hone her",answer:"sperm donor",hint:"baby charity"},
    {question:"hang ole sacks",answer:"anal sex",hint:"lube"},
    {question:"bull lay poem odd hull",answer:"playboy model",hint:"bunny"},
    {question:"foo cub bud tee",answer:"fuck buddy",hint:"u up"},
    {question:"fee core gas sum",answer:"fake orgasm",hint:"bed actress"},
    {question:"jake hut yum amuck cavey uh",answer:"shake what ya momma gave ya",hint:"moe ya bum"},
    {question:"dock keys tile",answer:"doggy style",hint:"ruff ruff"},
    {question:"aisle hike peg bus hike an hot done high",answer:"i like big butts and i cannot lie",hint:"can’t deny"},
    {question:"hue no hut the hays hay up out pick ands",answer:"you know what they say about big hands",hint:"large fingers"},
    {question:"hep pay ant ding",answer:"happy ending",hint:"joyous finale"},
    {question:"my grope bean his",answer:"micro penis",hint:"mini sausage"},
    {question:"try eave fin",answer:"dry heaving",hint:"no vom"},
    {question:"sec shoe holed inch in",answer:"sexual tension",hint:"tightrope"},
    {question:"pet oaf vial",answer:"pedophile",hint:"creep"},
    {question:"vole fur rental new did he",answer:"full frontal nudity",hint:"forward flashing"},
    {question:"sir gums his shin",answer:"circumcision",hint:"precise cut"},
    {question:"boo buzz wet",answer:"boob sweat",hint:"hot cleavage"},
    {question:"boat deke hall",answer:"booty call",hint:"that late text"},
    {question:"app heed rail",answer:"happy trail",hint:"hairy path"},
    {question:"nog tup",answer:"knocked up",hint:"preggo"},
    {question:"loaf fan dulls",answer:"love handles",hint:"well equipped"},
    {question:"loose eeyore fur chin knit he",answer:"lose your virginity",hint:"cherry on top"},
    {question:"slaw bees egg guns",answer:"sloppy seconds",hint:"silver medal"},
    {question:"mass tear bay gin",answer:"masturbation",hint:"self gratification"},
    {question:"wed he sured gone test",answer:"wet t shirt contest",hint:"see through"},
    {question:"sick shoe well lint hair gores",answer:"sexual intercourse",hint:"breeding"},
    {question:"wiz keyed hick",answer:"whiskey dick",hint:"floppy fish"},
    {question:"hoe more rag cur",answer:"homewrecker",hint:"moes burrito"},
    {question:"sum hag tad as",answer:"smack that ass",hint:"booty bop"},
    {question:"kid hang mite dig wed",answer:"getting my dick wet",hint:"underwater"},
    {question:"filet afford conned dumb",answer:"flavored condom",hint:"sweet safety"},
    {question:"hay read hose",answer:"hairy toes",hint:"feet fur"},
    {question:"gin hid all owe arts",answer:"genital warts",hint:"private pimples"},
    {question:"sell fur fogs",answer:"silver fox",hint:"gramps"},
    {question:"mourn ink have derp hill",answer:"morning after pill",hint:"safe not sorry"},
    {question:"bird they’s eggs",answer:"birthday sex",hint:"private present"},
    {question:"town nun doored he ",answer:"down and dirty",hint:"not up or clean"},
    {question:"sighed jig",answer:"side chick",hint:"hidden honey"},
    {question:"her ate it tar",answer:"rated R",hint:"says the pirate"},
    {question:"as seed inks ease on",answer:"ass eating season",hint:"periodic appetite"},
    {question:"less sum ache pay bays",answer:"lets make babies",hint:"reproduction"},
    {question:"hunk lie cohorts",answer:"hung like a horse",hint:"big baggage"},
    {question:"mean hut may inn",answer:"minute man",hint:"quick burst"},
    {question:"moth air hide lie who’ve ugg",answer:"mother id like to fuck",hint:"hi mom"},
    {question:"tad die dull hike dew fog",answer:"dad id like to fuck",hint:"hi pops"},
    {question:"won hint up ink doing thus tank",answer:"one in the pink two in the stink",hint:"versatile fingers"},
    {question:"bop ink dutch hairy",answer:"popping the cherry",hint:"first timer"},
    {question:"me ugh a leaf huh",answer:"mia khalifa",hint:"pornhub"},{question:"range imp owner",answer:"raging boner",hint:"very erect"},
    {question:"bus seal hick king",answer:"pussy licking",hint:"cat tasting"}
    ]
    
const mixDeck=[

    {question:"stirrup oak her",answer:"strip poker",hint:"naked games"},
    {question:"bud dish hots",answer:"body shots",hint:"belly button"},
    {question:"parr grr all",answer:"bar crawl",hint:"on to the next"},
    {question:"mails drip her",answer:"male stripper",hint:"dollar bills"},
    {question:"hug cup called sure",answer:"hookup culture",hint:"sleeping around"},
    {question:"bod dull hope inner",answer:"bottle opener",hint:"cork"},
    {question:"half dare bar tee",answer:"after party",hint:"round 2"},
    {question:"trunk cog holes",answer:"drunk goggles",hint:"tipsy eyes"},
    {question:"way camp ache",answer:"wake and bake",hint:"off to a good start"},
    {question:"pod pro niece",answer:"pot brownies",hint:"chill chocolate"},
    {question:"diss sicken ate it rif e her",answer:"designated driver",hint:"the real MVP tonight"},
    {question:"ford went he",answer:"420",hint:"national holiday"},
    {question:"pup of as",answer:"puff puff pass",hint:"joint instructions"},
    {question:"may get train",answer:"make it rain",hint:"good weather"},
    {question:"past hutch owe ain't",answer:"pass the joint",hint:"split the pot"},
    {question:"shod game ink appear",answer:"shotgunning a beer",hint:"quick drink"},
    {question:"par dave owl",answer:"party foul",hint:"socially unacceptable"},
    {question:"can ebb hiss",answer:"cannabis",hint:"like MJ"},
    {question:"ha tub ox sing",answer:"hot boxing",hint:"foggy car"},
    {question:"hid tub pong",answer:"hit the bong",hint:"bike toke"},
    {question:"wad herb pong",answer:"water bong",hint:"purified smoke"},
    {question:"read soul oak up",answer:"red solo cup",hint:"beer pong"},
    {question:"jew wool bod",answer:"juulpod",hint:"new cigs"},
    {question:"graph tub here",answer:"craft beer",hint:"not bud light"},
    {question:"spend tub ought all",answer:"spin the bottle",hint:"kiss kiss"},
    {question:"bought til cervix",answer:"bottle service",hint:"grey goose"},
    {question:"due rug tess",answer:"drug test",hint:"pee cup"},
    {question:"fizz dub hum bing",answer:"fist pumping",hint:"clubbing"},
    {question:"moan cheese",answer:"munchies",hint:"hangry"},
    {question:"tech heel huts hot",answer:"tequila shot",hint:"lots of lime"},
    {question:"read bow fog caw",answer:"redbull vodka",hint:"classic combo"},
    {question:"score be on pole",answer:"scorpion bowl",hint:"group drink"},
    {question:"pod tum mull his minnows us",answer:"bottomless mimosas",hint:"brunch"},
    {question:"drub bet lie kits sot",answer:"drop it like its hot",hint:"snooooop"},
    {question:"napper half fie heifer",answer:"never have i ever",hint:"secrets told"},
    {question:"ball hack doubt",answer:"blacked out",hint:"drunken darkness"},
    {question:"cram pear heave ought caw",answer:"cranberry vodka",hint:"spiked juice"},
    {question:"tab pith hug egg",answer:"tap the egg",hint:"pour the beer"},
    {question:"pinch shrink gang",answer:"binge drinking",hint:"dedicated hydration"},
    {question:"barrel limp picks",answer:"beer olympics",hint:"local competition"},
    {question:"furl oak hoe",answer:"four loko",hint:"banned substance"},
    {question:"far tin gimp up lick",answer:"farting in public",hint:"noisy outside"},
    {question:"bogs due i’m",answer:"boxed wine",hint:"franzia"},
    {question:"hank oaf irk your",answer:"hangover cure",hint:"sunday medication"},
    {question:"paw where our",answer:"power hour",hint:"beer timer"},
    {question:"sog key pom",answer:"sake bomb",hint:"beer cocktail"},
    {question:"jane’s moat king",answer:"chain smoking",hint:"lotta butts"},
    {question:"fay guy tee",answer:"fake id",hint:"golden ticket"},
    {question:"bob ping bought tolls",answer:"popping bottles",hint:"champagne"},
    {question:"app he yeah war",answer:"happy hour",hint:"joyous time"},
    {question:"pain yuck hole odd huh",answer:"pina colada",hint:"pineapple punch"},
    {question:"dirt rugged heel her",answer:"drug dealer",hint:"weed"},
    {question:"thor tier hack",answer:"30 rack",hint:"bud light"},
    {question:"saws itch barred hay",answer:"sausage party",hint:"all male"},
    {question:"dare team art teenie",answer:"dirty martini",hint:"not clean"},
    {question:"zig are wet",answer:"cigarette",hint:"juul"},
    {question:"peer belle he",answer:"beer belly",hint:"too much bud"},
    {question:"mark car eat duh",answer:"margarita",hint:"salty rim"},
    {question:"room manned coat",answer:"rum and coke",hint:"classic combo"},
    {question:"shale low shods",answer:"jello shots",hint:"dessert drink"},
    {question:"prow nowed",answer:"brown out",hint:"one too many"},
    {question:"raw link babe hair",answer:"rolling paper",hint:"green accessory"},
    {question:"tea ages he",answer:"thc",hint:"hippie chemistry"},
    {question:"kay gust and",answer:"keg stand",hint:"tap it"},
    {question:"foal hip cub",answer:"flip cup",hint:"red solo"},
    {question:"hog tote bear vest",answer:"oktoberfest",hint:"bier"},
    {question:"gin dairy feel barred tee",answer:"gender reveal party",hint:"pink or blue"},
    {question:"trunk eggs stink",answer:"drunk texting",hint:"idk where i am"},
    {question:"seep peed he wile",answer:"cbd oil",hint:"for anxiety"},
    {question:"past hutch owe ain’t",answer:"pass the joint",hint:"split the pot"},
    {question:"shod gone ink appear",answer:"shotgunning a beer",hint:"quick drink"},

    {question:"fit he sheds off cray",answer:"fifty shades of grey",hint:"whips and chain"},  {question:"core run teen",answer:"quarantine",hint:"’rona"},
    {question:"cuh rone ahvi rust",answer:"corona virus",hint:"'rona"},
    {question:"suhw ayp reyt",answer:"swipe right",hint:"’she/hes hottt"},
       {question:"fog chair he",answer:"fuckjerry",hint:"meme account"},
       {question:"guy leech hen her",answer:"kylie jenner",hint:"makeup"},
       {question:"trick her worn in",answer:"trigger warning",hint:"alert"},
       {question:"crap temp eye tub pushy",answer:"grab them by the pussy",hint:"trump advice"},
       {question:"nun she ammo",answer:"non gmo",hint:"nutrition"},
       {question:"hatch meows hide hobo dad",answer:"catch me outside how about that",hint:"dr. phil"},
       {question:"fish hits bin hers",answer:"fidget spinners",hint:"rotating distraction"},
       {question:"hue own lee leaf ones",answer:"you only live once",hint:"limited existence"},
       {question:"day yam tan knee hole",answer:"damn daniel",hint:"white vans"},
       {question:"knit flick sand shill",answer:"netflix and chill",hint:"watching movies"},
       {question:"sad hurt ace surf forth a voice",answer:"saturdays are for the boys",hint:"barstool sports"},
       {question:"chut ches lied",answer:"cha cha slide",hint:"wedding moves"},
       {question:"their heels limp shed he",answer:"the real slim shady",hint:"eminem"},
       {question:"sid hop drying tomb ache kvetch have been",answer:"stop trying to make fetch happen",hint:"regina george"},
       {question:"own wind stays weave hair ping",answer:"on wednesdays, we wear pink",hint:"weekly color preference"},
       {question:"hid sprint heap itch",answer:"its britney bitch",hint:"oops! I did it again"},
       {question:"veer off mess sing oat",answer:"fear of missing out",hint:"social anxiety"},
       {question:"this drug gull israel",answer:"the struggle is real",hint:"first world problems"},
       {question:"hint turn ed rolls",answer:"internet trolls",hint:"online bullies"},
       {question:"real agents sip gulls",answer:"relationship goals",hint:"power couple"},
       {question:"hike ant eve hen",answer:"i cant even",hint:"ugh, whatever"},
       {question:"per rake tee inner ned",answer:"break the internet",hint:"crash the web"},
       {question:"boy full leash awe",answer:"bye felicia",hint:"adios, amiga"},
       {question:"hey dares con a hayed",answer:"haters gonna hate",hint:"critics criticize"},
       {question:"hay knob putty god dime fourth hat",answer:"aint nobody got time for that",hint:"i got bronchitis"},
       {question:"tad swat cheese head",answer:"thats what she said",hint:"classic response"},
       {question:"razzled ding pitch vase",answer:"resting bitch face",hint:"lingering facial rage"},
       {question:"fifed holler food lawn",answer:"5 dollar footlong",hint:"eat fresh"},
       {question:"hints tug rams hole leper hid tea",answer:"instagram celebrity",hint:"internet famous"},
       {question:"dez pus seed hoe",answer:"despacito",hint:"taquito, dorito"},
       {question:"ham a sauna let’s uh",answer:"amazon alexa",hint:"robot commands"},
       {question:"stir range earth inks",answer:"stranger things",hint:"upside down"},
       {question:"came off drones",answer:"game of thrones",hint:"iron throne"},
       {question:"brute teen pout her",answer:"protein powder",hint:"strong sugar"},
       {question:"sun nap chad’s door he",answer:"snapchat story",hint:"24-hour special"},
       {question:"hints toe cram starry",answer:"instagram story",hint:"no filter"},
       {question:"hud yolk uh",answer:"hot yoga",hint:"warm stretching"},
       {question:"hoop purr pull",answer:"uber pool",hint:"shared ride"},
       {question:"tethers diss rail",answer:"the thirst is real",hint:"parched"},
       {question:"bull lag fried hay",answer:"black friday",hint:"crazy shopping"},
       {question:"aight hook uphill henna bees uh",answer:"i took a pill in ibiza",hint:"mike posner"},
       {question:"sure gore furry",answer:"sugar free",hint:"boring alternative"},
       {question:"glide much henge",answer:"climate change",hint:"carbon crisis"},
       {question:"cause mob hole lid in",answer:"cosmopolitan",hint:"drink and mag"},
       {question:"king cord ash yen whizzed",answer:"kim kardashian west",hint:"keeping up"},
       {question:"mic cup two door real",answer:"makeup tutorial",hint:"beauty 101"},
       {question:"tint hurt eight",answer:"tinder date",hint:"it’s a match"},
       {question:"purr roam hands",answer:"bromance",hint:"i love you, man"},
       {question:"bell who awful",answer:"blue waffle",hint:"fake STD"},
       {question:"wear caw haul leg",answer:"workaholic",hint:"job addicted"},
       {question:"freak when doff liar my holes",answer:"frequent flyer miles",hint:"united airlines"},
       {question:"huh verb oar duh",answer:"hoverboard",hint:"scooter"},
       {question:"prix aunt kush hoe bra",answer:"priyanka chopra",hint:"bollywood"},
       {question:"sate donut spur aid hit",answer:"say it dont spray it",hint:"saliva"},
       {question:"glow eek hard ashy am",answer:"khloe kardashian",hint:"keeping up"},
       {question:"vector hero yell",answer:"victory royale",hint:"fortnite"},
       {question:"ton hold romp shoe near",answer:"donald trump jr",hint:"son of a"},
       {question:"mime elks ache brim saul dubai’s tooth uh yod",answer:"my milkshake brings all the boys to the yard",hint:"booty shake"},
       {question:"huge act mend",answer:"hugh jackman",hint:"wolverine"},
       {question:"why and ran holds",answer:"ryan reynolds",hint:"actor"},
       {question:"bay beam on uh",answer:"baby mama",hint:"parent"},
       {question:"debt tub bool",answer:"deadpool",hint:"superhero"},
       {question:"tech a gel pal",answer:"take a chill pill",hint:"overreacting"},
       {question:"star mead annuals",answer:"stormy daniels",hint:"bad weather"},
       {question:"foot comb uh",answer:"food coma",hint:"thanksgiving"},
       {question:"fenced a hug hound",answer:"finsta account",hint:"second profile"},
       {question:"tech get mads tear",answer:"ticketmaster",hint:"event boss"},
       {question:"yeah skew ween",answer:"yas queen",hint:"you go girl"},
       {question:"knew foam hood is",answer:"new phone who dis",hint:"no contacts"},
       {question:"croupe miss itch",answer:"group message",hint:"text us"},
       {question:"furry wife eye",answer:"free wifi",hint:"starbucks"},
       {question:"stuff fin cure ray",answer:"stephen curry",hint:"MVP"},
       {question:"iowa cope lie hiss",answer:"i woke up like this",hint:"flawless"},
       {question:"soak wad coals",answer:"squad goals",hint:"cool kids"},
       {question:"gash shole knee",answer:"cash only",hint:"ATM"},
       {question:"for tea your all diversion",answer:"40 year old virgin",hint:"steve carell"},
       {question:"had meow null ink den",answer:"add me on linkedin",hint:"networking"},
       {question:"jews cull lens",answer:"juice cleanse",hint:"liquid health"},
       {question:"of venture sin fin it you oar",answer:"avengers infinite war",hint:"thanos"},
       {question:"whole avant form wrist mist issue",answer:"all i want for christmas is you",hint:"mariah"},
       {question:"furry dude aid chip ping",answer:"free 2 day shipping",hint:"prime target"},
       {question:"hue nick horn fir rap bush sheen owe",answer:"unicorn frappuccino",hint:"magical drink"},
       {question:"broke he monk hoe",answer:"pokemon go",hint:"pikachu"},
       {question:"stir hate owe dug humped in",answer:"straight outta compton",hint:"ice cube"},
       {question:"clue tin furry",answer:"gluten free",hint:"fake bread"},
       {question:"died botch ill hinge",answer:"tide pod challenge",hint:"eating soap"},
       {question:"mocks suck curb berk",answer:"mark zuckerberg",hint:"news feed"},
       {question:"sue why bride",answer:"swipe right",hint:"it’s a match"},
       {question:"set ton owe won heifer",answer:"said no one ever",hint:"snarky reply"},
       {question:"key bit won hunt rid",answer:"keep it 100",hint:"the real deal"},
       {question:"pitch pull ease",answer:"bitch please!",hint:"finger snap"},
       {question:"tour king",answer:"twerking",hint:"modern shake"},
       {question:"aim his own burr rhyme",answer:"amazon prime",hint:"bezos"},
       {question:"walk hun dove oar ev her",answer:"wakanda forever",hint:"east africa"},
       {question:"fur stew hurled prop plums",answer:"first world problems",hint:"not real issues"},
       {question:"comp hooch ya",answer:"kombucha",hint:"drink fad"},
       {question:"birch who’ll ray yell lid he",answer:"virtual reality",hint:"fake life"},
       {question:"sun nab shat filled her",answer:"snapchat filter",hint:"virtual makeup"},
       {question:"van heap hack",answer:"fanny pack",hint:"strap-on fashion"},
       {question:"bore dare well",answer:"border wall",hint:"trump’s fence"},
       {question:"shelf dry fink curse",answer:"self driving cars",hint:"robo wheels"},
       {question:"that he itch use",answer:"daddy issues",hint:"father probs"},
       {question:"ran shore blush ease",answer:"ranch or blue cheese?",hint:"buffalo wings"},
       {question:"two huey fen lived pro",answer:"do you even lift bro?",hint:"gym membership"},
       {question:"quack his sex draw",answer:"guac is extra",hint:"chipotle"},
       {question:"mayan knock honda toned",answer:"my anaconda don’t",hint:"nicki"},
       {question:"aims heck see hand eye note",answer:"i’m sexy and i know it",hint:"hot and confident"},
       {question:"burn niece handlers",answer:"bernie sanders",hint:"universal healthcare"},
       {question:"pressed feet tin",answer:"breast feeding",hint:"milk"},
       {question:"yen if hearse sale elf kay her",answer:"universal healthcare",hint:"total support"},
       {question:"crib took her rinse see",answer:"cryptocurrency",hint:"fake moola"},
       {question:"boo pay moat she",answer:"poop emoji",hint:"smelly smile"},
       {question:"slight tint huey ore tea hems",answer:"slide into your dms",hint:"pickup line"},
       {question:"vague noose",answer:"fake news",hint:"legit info"},
       {question:"ellen mayo",answer:"lmao",hint:"cracking up"},
       {question:"foe dope bum",answer:"photobomb",hint:"exploding image"},
       {question:"call ick bayed",answer:"clickbait",hint:"headliner"},
       {question:"womb hank rush when stay",answer:"women crush wednesday",hint:"hump day"},
       {question:"mank rush moaned hay",answer:"man crush monday",hint:"weekly bf post"},
       {question:"go shell law",answer:"coachella",hint:"getting festive"},
       {question:"pars duels boards",answer:"barstool sports",hint:"boston blog"},
       {question:"huff fog autoed host",answer:"avocado toast",hint:"best breakfast"},
       {question:"check hen nan due awfuls",answer:"chicken and waffles",hint:"soul food"},
       {question:"bump ken spies slot day",answer:"pumpkin spice latte",hint:"basic caffeine"},
       {question:"hids nod hue wets may",answer:"its not you its me",hint:"breakup"},
       {question:"thorough winks aid",answer:"throwing shade",hint:"tossing insults"},
       {question:"bush rop raw",answer:"push up bra",hint:" lifted"},
       {question:"mere ores elf fee",answer:"mirror selfie",hint:"reflection"},
       {question:"sore hay nods ore hee",answer:"sorry not sorry",hint:"no apology"},
       {question:"buffers toll led meat ache us elf fee",answer:"but first let me take a selfie",hint:"wait snap a pic"},
       {question:"whirls tar rip pop",answer:"worldstar hiphop",hint:"fight videos"},
       {question:"bays sig up hitch",answer:"basic bitch",hint:"standard human"},
       {question:"duke earls swung up",answer:"two girls one cup",hint:"shit you can’t unsee"},
       {question:"beep perve favor",answer:"bieber fever",hint:"canadian sickness"},
       {question:"cough inks ease in",answer:"cuffing season",hint:"wintertime"},
       {question:"shake fur rum stayed of harm",answer:"jake from state farm",hint:"khaki model"},
       {question:"a dull thing",answer:"adulting",hint:"grown-up"},
       {question:"car mush up itch",answer:"karmas a bitch",hint:"cause and effect"},
       {question:"starred if rum tub pot hum",answer:"started from the bottom",hint:"no privilege"},
       {question:"stalk hint of rends own",answer:"stuck in the friend zone",hint:"high five!"},
       {question:"thor dwee link",answer:"third wheeling",hint:"here for support"},
       {question:"dean mage purr wreck nun see",answer:"teenage pregnancy",hint:"young momma"},
       {question:"fun dizzy food pall",answer:"fantasy football",hint:"gambling"},
       {question:"pow hurk up pull",answer:"power couple",hint:"perfect pair"},
       {question:"sups cur ripe tomb eye sham null",answer:"subscribe to my channel",hint:"youtube"},
       {question:"jenner agency",answer:"generation z",hint:"up-and-coming"},
       {question:"cape gall manned care ray han",answer:"keep calm and carry on",hint:"poster"},
       {question:"fret shim in fit teen",answer:"freshman fifteen",hint:"collegiate perks"},
       {question:"ma shawl hot hey",answer:"matcha latte",hint:"new drink fad"},
       {question:"purry war cowed",answer:"pre workout",hint:"before lifting"},
       {question:"cell fees tick",answer:"selfie stick",hint:"photo assistant"},
       {question:"egg straw hay elf",answer:"extra af",hint:"so additional"},
       {question:"enter net vain muss",answer:"internet famous",hint:"known online"},
       {question:"sums how’d gums shout",answer:"suns out guns out",hint:"tank top"},
       {question:"shy hold dish camp he no",answer:"childish gambino",hint:"rapper"},
       {question:"ump hate hint urn zip",answer:"unpaid internship",hint:"college student"},
       {question:"the row pack thirst hay",answer:"throwback thursday",hint:"weekly memz"},
       {question:"cape in cup width hug hard ashy ins",answer:"keeping up with the kardashians",hint:"guilty pleasure"},
       {question:"wet thing seize hen",answer:"wedding season",hint:"promising series"},
       {question:"ike hot if rum mime hum uh",answer:"i got it from my momma",hint:"in my DNA"},
       {question:"odd doe core egged",answer:"autocorrect",hint:"text replacement"},
       {question:"bin joe wad shin",answer:"binge watching",hint:"tv marathon"},
       {question:"lung air toned gayer",answer:"long hair dont care",hint:"lovely locks"},
       {question:"can mold oh",answer:"camel toe",hint:"sahara foot"},
       {question:"sill lab hiss wake",answer:"syllabus week",hint:"new semester"},
       {question:"ron men newt holes",answer:"ramen noodles",hint:"american delicacy"},
       {question:"fife oak log chad hoe",answer:"five oclock shadow",hint:"short stubble"},
       {question:"pie juan kit won furry",answer:"buy 1 get 1 free",hint:"gmail promotion"},
       {question:"dime sinew roam men",answer:"times new roman",hint:"MLA format"},
       {question:"moor nim bur wrath",answer:"morning breath",hint:"wake-up smell"},
       {question:"snap bowl fax",answer:"snapple facts",hint:"liquid knowledge"},
       {question:"chest who wit",answer:"just do it",hint:"global slogan"},
       {question:"her pinned ick shun hairy",answer:"urban dictionary",hint:"fun meanings"},
       {question:"food cub hitches skit moan hay",answer:"fuck bitches get money",hint:"ignorant motto"},
       {question:"race sore perm",answer:"razor burn",hint:"shaving sucks"},
       {question:"hid scum plug hated",answer:"its complicated",hint:"relationship status"},
       {question:"lib full half all of",answer:"live laugh love",hint:"another poster quote"},
       {question:"dome hutch chin firm hey shun",answer:"too much information",hint:"but why"},
       {question:"a dent chum hoe were",answer:"attention whore",hint:"fame obsessed"},
       {question:"hope in real asian ship",answer:"open relationship",hint:"extramarital"},
       {question:"carp pull carry oak he",answer:"carpool karaoke",hint:"sing-along"},
       {question:"heir being bee",answer:"airbnb",hint:"couch surfing"},
       {question:"wind her ritz cum ink",answer:"winter is coming",hint:"snow"},
       {question:"tub hatch chill or wet",answer:"the bachelorette",hint:"love olympics"},
       {question:"kin trick loam are",answer:"kendrick lamar",hint:"DAMN."},
       {question:"shams there ab her",answer:"chance the rapper",hint:"probability"},
       {question:"neck key men notch",answer:"nicki minaj",hint:"anaconda"},
       {question:"cart he pea",answer:"cardi b",hint:"okurrrr"},
       {question:"gone yay whizzed",answer:"kanye west",hint:"genius"},
       {question:"dutch aims mole curse",answer:"the chainsmokers",hint:"cigarettes"},
       {question:"duh hammed mate stale",answer:"the handmaids tale",hint:"hulu"},
       {question:"if hung cut romp",answer:"ivanka trump",hint:"#1 daughter"},
       {question:"he’ll lawn mosque",answer:"elon musk",hint:"iron man"},
       {question:"hum pull bore rag",answer:"humble brag",hint:"sneaky ego"},
       {question:"phase bucks tall king",answer:"facebook stalking",hint:"social spy"},
       {question:"trains form agent who’s stay",answer:"transformation tuesday",hint:"insta ritual"},
       {question:"ham ions peak her",answer:"am i on speaker",hint:"loud phone"},
       {question:"wads thaw why vibe ass sword",answer:"what’s the wifi password",hint:"saving data"},
       {question:"bay purse draws",answer:"paper straws",hint:"eco-friendly"},
       {question:"whip stone dull hi",answer:"hips don’t lie",hint:"shakira"},
       {question:"low roll or yam knee",answer:"laurel or yanny",hint:"listen close"},
       {question:"son dane knived vote bowl",answer:"sunday night football",hint:"wings and pizza"},
       {question:"sit orange his alm oats fool",answer:"storage is almost full",hint:"need memory"},
       {question:"reed seating air lime",answer:"receding hairline",hint:"growing forehead"},
       {question:"cub hulls mesh hutch",answer:"couples massage",hint:"all the feels"},
       {question:"burr thick hunt roll",answer:"birth control",hint:"sexual safety"},
       {question:"red ray seeds",answer:"read receipts",hint:"imessage"},
       {question:"yolk hub ants",answer:"yoga pants",hint:"tight and comfy"},
       {question:"are he amuck ran day",answer:"ariana grande",hint:"ponytail"},
       {question:"shone ham knit tee",answer:"sean hannity",hint:"foxy"},
       {question:"men him hum owe age",answer:"minimum wage",hint:"per hour"},
       {question:"hoop heard rife fair",answer:"uber driver",hint:"5 stars"},
       {question:"pray kink how’d",answer:"breaking out",hint:"puberty"},
       {question:"eel lips sob bath wear in",answer:"elizabeth warren",hint:"native american"},
       {question:"gunk on troll",answer:"gun control",hint:"amendment"},
       {question:"brick gnat seed hest",answer:"pregnancy test",hint:"plus or minus"},
       {question:"eggs plows if dire hey ya",answer:"explosive diarrhea",hint:"boom toilet"},
       {question:"eggs pox sole i’ve",answer:"xbox live",hint:"video game"},
       {question:"fork hop as whirred",answer:"forgot password",hint:"username"},
       {question:"bore he’d dope pole",answer:"burrito bowl",hint:"chipotle"},
       {question:"ink hog knead ode",answer:"incognito mode",hint:"secret search"},
       {question:"far rat turn it heap rod her",answer:"fraternity brother",hint:"greekish"},
       {question:"full hi yank sole low",answer:"flying solo",hint:"free like a bird"},
       {question:"hen newest fill led dale fear porn hand raced",answer:"in west philadelphia born and raised",hint:"bel air"},
       {question:"stood den dead",answer:"student debt",hint:"so college"},
       {question:"calf itched",answer:"catfished",hint:"fake ID"},
       {question:"meh come air ick auger rate akin",answer:"make america great again",hint:"on a red hat"},
       {question:"hill loom men hottie",answer:"illuminati",hint:"beyonce"},
       {question:"shin me fail on",answer:"jimmy fallon",hint:"late night"},
       {question:"awed toad dune",answer:"autotune",hint:"t-pain"},
       {question:"lint seal owe hand",answer:"lindsay lohan",hint:"parent trap"},
       {question:"lug would chew mate made who",answer:"look what you made me do",hint:"swift"},
       {question:"brr had leak hoop her",answer:"bradley cooper",hint:"a star is born"},
       {question:"torn town furrow hut",answer:"turn down for what",hint:"lil jon"},
       {question:"hone limed agree",answer:"online degree",hint:"phoenix"},
       {question:"fifes heck gunned roll",answer:"five second rule",hint:"safe to eat"},
       {question:"check full hay",answer:"chick fil a",hint:"christian food"},
       {question:"coal ledge job how’d",answer:"college dropout",hint:"zuckerberg"},
       {question:"bus so feat",answer:"buzzfeed",hint:"online quiz"},
       {question:"eighty age tee",answer:"adhd",hint:"can’t sit still"},
       {question:"we’re duh flax bud oak hay",answer:"weird flex but ok",hint:"show off"},
       {question:"beer purr retch her",answer:"peer pressure",hint:"c’mon, do it"},
       {question:"fair if i’d hook hound",answer:"verified account",hint:"blue check mark"},
       {question:"hints stuck ramp gap shin",answer:"instagram caption",hint:"subtitle"},
       {question:"son herb pod",answer:"summer bod",hint:"six pack"},
       {question:"phase poke off his shoal",answer:"facebook official",hint:"in a relationship"},
       {question:"burrows pea four rose",answer:"bros before hoes",hint:"fratty motto"},
       {question:"coal brook off he",answer:"cold brew coffee",hint:"icy caffeine"},
       {question:"pig sore hit tint tap open",answer:"pics or it didnt happen",hint:"picture proof"},
       {question:"haze sear ray",answer:"hey siri",hint:"personal assistant"},
       {question:"pole lid tick glee anchor wrecked",answer:"politically incorrect",hint:"offensive"},
       {question:"hall moan dumb elk",answer:"almond milk",hint:"nutty drink"},
       {question:"shoals hike hole",answer:"soulcycle",hint:"bike club"},
       {question:"heart fish hole and hell itch hens",answer:"artificial intelligence",hint:"fake smart"},
       {question:"herb pam how’d tvet hers",answer:"urban outfitters",hint:"cool clothes"},
       {question:"ab pole moose sick",answer:"apple music",hint:"fruit tunes"},
       {question:"shone meant diss",answer:"shawn mendes",hint:"in my blood"},
       {question:"pose dumb alone",answer:"post malone",hint:"face tats"},
       {question:"meat whom hoove mint",answer:"me too movement",hint:"time’s up"},
       {question:"sack jewel lorry hen day chin",answer:"sexual orientation",hint:"born this way"},
       {question:"hay thee yes sim",answer:"atheism",hint:"ungodly"},
       {question:"pot turn knit teed hest",answer:"paternity test",hint:"maury"},
       {question:"rush a knack king",answer:"russian hacking",hint:"interference"},
       {question:"fray dome muffs beach",answer:"freedom of speech",hint:"say whatcha want"},
       {question:"sigh burp pully inn",answer:"cyber bullying",hint:"virtual villain"},
       {question:"ache quill bay",answer:"equal pay",hint:"every dollar counts"},
       {question:"calf finned her ant",answer:"kevin durant",hint:"top baller"},
       {question:"low camp haul",answer:"logan paul",hint:"social media star"},
       {question:"press hid hinder ump",answer:"president trump",hint:"orange face"},
       {question:"jim tam lawn tree",answer:"gym tan laundry",hint:"jersey shore"},
       {question:"rope herd mule lore",answer:"robert mueller",hint:"special detective"},
       {question:"kin chaw noon",answer:"kim jong un",hint:"rocket man"},
       {question:"kin you’ve hem mow mi",answer:"can you venmo me",hint:"split the bill"},
       {question:"vie her vest if all",answer:"fyre festival",hint:"fake event"},
       {question:"snake her reds",answer:"sneakerheads",hint:"new shoes"},
       {question:"him pea chum mint",answer:"impeachment",hint:"mueller"},

       {question:"digs a king libs",answer:"dick sucking",hint:"orally gifted"},
       {question:"bra silly anne whacks",answer:"brazilian wax",hint:"beach trimming"},
       {question:"hid thud she’s pot",answer:"hit the g spot",hint:"bull’s eye"},
       {question:"lab bud ants",answer:"lap dance",hint:"paid ride"},
       {question:"rivers scowl curl",answer:"reverse cowgirl",hint:"backward rider"},
       {question:"tub bullpen hid race sun",answer:"double penetration",hint:"extra stuffed"},
       {question:"cold hen chow hair",answer:"golden shower",hint:"urinating hygiene"},
       {question:"bud pull lug",answer:"butt plug",hint:"clog the hole"},
       {question:"say foe herd",answer:"safe word",hint:"backup plan"},
       {question:"duh heep their oat",answer:"deep throat",hint:"all in"},
       {question:"toggled hurt heat whom he",answer:"talk dirty to me",hint:"naughty language"},
       {question:"call it tour his",answer:"clitoris",hint:"sex organ"},
       {question:"six zoo wing",answer:"sex wing",hint:"playground toy"},
       {question:"men nog gummy",answer:"monogamy",hint:"locked down"},
       {question:"though wok calves aim",answer:"the walk of shame",hint:"morning-after stroll"},
       {question:"cop bull logged",answer:"cockblocked",hint:"unwanted defense"},
       {question:"dig beer zing",answer:"dick piercing",hint:"sausage ring"},
       {question:"offer dub ant sand chop",answer:"over the pants hand job",hint:"heavy-duty rub"},
       {question:"in flay doubles hex tall",answer:"inflatable sex doll",hint:"blow-up partner"},
       {question:"loop reek hand",answer:"lubricant",hint:"slippery"},
       {question:"his cat tin ought inner ear",answer:"its getting hot in here",hint:"nelly"},
       {question:"heated tank wit id",answer:"hit it and quit it",hint:"one time"},
       {question:"four neg age in",answer:"fornication",hint:"under the covers"},
       {question:"keg reef flux",answer:"gag reflex",hint:"taking it all in"},
       {question:"dig kin hub ox",answer:"dick in a box",hint:"boxed sausage"},
       {question:"ore holes eggs",answer:"sex oral",hint:"going down"},
       {question:"bud make it",answer:"butt naked",hint:"nice buns"},
       {question:"sack son deb each",answer:"sex on the beach",hint:"fun in the sun"},
       {question:"sin goal lander head eat who mink goal",answer:"single and ready to mingle",hint:"flying solo"},
       {question:"trees hum",answer:"threesome",hint:"kinky trio"},
       {question:"bop login draw pit",answer:"pop lock and drop it",hint:"dance it"},
       {question:"cut dull putty",answer:"cuddle buddy",hint:"snuggling"},
       {question:"fur rents switch pen of its",answer:"friends with benefits",hint:"keeping it casual"},
       {question:"fairy kin tush eats",answer:"freak in the sheets",hint:"kinky underwear"},
       {question:"deep hag king",answer:"tea bagging",hint:"not coffee"},
       {question:"he’d check you’ll hay shin",answer:"ejaculation",hint:"milky discharge"},
       {question:"pour bot hem",answer:"power bottom",hint:"lower strength"},
       {question:"bay or bags hex",answer:"bareback sex",hint:"unprotected"},
       {question:"glow ray hull",answer:"glory hole",hint:"anonymous pleasure"},
       {question:"zoo wing or potty",answer:"swinger party",hint:"orgy hangout"},
       {question:"sex sigh hold",answer:"sexiled",hint:"kicked out"},
       {question:"calm heed at tea",answer:"call me daddy",hint:"labeled father"},
       {question:"drow gin gone dumbs",answer:"trojan condoms",hint:"rubbers"},
       {question:"den hinged hill though",answer:"10 inch dildo",hint:"lengthy load"},
       {question:"lay sunder weigh her",answer:"lace underwear",hint:"cheeky panties"},
       {question:"aim null zoo thing shell",answer:"anal soothing gel",hint:"tushy blue"},
       {question:"full less shell lied",answer:"fleshlight",hint:"male masturbator"},
       {question:"sir cull shirk",answer:"circle jerk",hint:"helping hands"},
       {question:"six dang",answer:"sexting",hint:"snapchat"},
       {question:"muh knees hot",answer:"money shot",hint:"booming dollar"},
       {question:"din call parry",answer:"dingleberry",hint:"hairy problem"},
       {question:"heck plan team owe gee",answer:"eggplant emoji",hint:"not a vegetable"},
       {question:"pea gym mow she",answer:"peach emoji",hint:"animated butt"},
       {question:"high juan shoe-ins height off may",answer:"i want you inside of me",hint:"polite request"},
       {question:"bore knock rough he",answer:"pornography",hint:"incognito window"},
       {question:"high lie kit her of",answer:"i like it rough",hint:"masochism"},
       {question:"stirp hip purple",answer:"stripper pole",hint:"metallic tool"},
       {question:"chad drool hat",answer:"chatroulette",hint:"random strangers"},
       {question:"aim hole beets",answer:"anal beads",hint:"booty jewelry"},
       {question:"sent ink newts",answer:"sending nudes",hint:"photo text"},
       {question:"show dub pant kids meh",answer:"shut up and kiss me",hint:"quiet makeout"},
       {question:"sped doors wall hoe",answer:"spit or swallow",hint:"BJ thoughts"},
       {question:"mourn hang would",answer:"morning wood",hint:"sunrise surprise"},
       {question:"shook herd addie",answer:"sugar daddy",hint:"sweet father"},
       {question:"purry match hurry shack yule asian",answer:"premature ejaculation",hint:"too soon"},
       {question:"pick tick kin hurt she",answer:"big dick energy",hint:"cocky"},
       {question:"pants eggs shoe well",answer:"pansexual",hint:"all on the table"},
       {question:"hay reap you bus",answer:"hairy pubes",hint:"jungle down under"},
       {question:"book hockey",answer:"bukkake",hint:"group effort"},
       {question:"don’t hoof hug",answer:"down to fuck",hint:"yes/no question"},
       {question:"for wren shuck his sing",answer:"french kissing",hint:"eiffel tower"},
       {question:"hey null fish ding",answer:"anal fisting",hint:"high give in the back"},
       {question:"who ed reams",answer:"wet dreams",hint:"slippery sleep"},
       {question:"sicks teen hine",answer:"69",hint:"team work"},
       {question:"miss shun hairy boss itch shun",answer:"missionary position",hint:"starter pose"},
       {question:"sid ton knife ace",answer:"sit on my face",hint:"vip seats"},
       {question:"fay club oops",answer:"fake boobs",hint:"plastic"},
       {question:"nom pen hit rate ifs eggs",answer:"non penetrative sex",hint:"outercourse"},
       {question:"as tomb out",answer:"ass to mouth",hint:"taste of booty"},
       {question:"orc gasp him",answer:"orgasm",hint:"pleasant finish"},
       {question:"hiss sit tinny it",answer:"is it in yet",hint:"tiny tim"},
       {question:"poll lick come me",answer:"polygamy",hint:"free bird"},
       {question:"ear reptile this funk sheen",answer:"erectile dysfunction",hint:"get up plz"},
       {question:"try yum bing",answer:"dry humping",hint:"clothed sex"},
       {question:"hey rig runt tell",answer:"hair grundle",hint:"jungle butt"},
       {question:"food fed dish",answer:"foot fetish",hint:"tasty toes"},
       {question:"tom mean hay tricks",answer:"dominatrix",hint:"naughty boss"},
       {question:"sit drab pond hill though",answer:"strap on dildo",hint:"sexcessory"},
       {question:"nib pull peers sing",answer:"nipple piercing",hint:"body jewel"},
       {question:"chow wears hex",answer:"shower sex",hint:"waterfall"},
       {question:"unhides tanned",answer:"one night stand",hint:"in and out"},
       {question:"spur mud hone her",answer:"sperm donor",hint:"baby charity"},
       {question:"hang ole sacks",answer:"anal sex",hint:"lube"},
       {question:"bull lay poem odd hull",answer:"playboy model",hint:"bunny"},
       {question:"foo cub bud tee",answer:"fuck buddy",hint:"u up"},
       {question:"fee core gas sum",answer:"fake orgasm",hint:"bed actress"},
       {question:"jake hut yum amuck cavey uh",answer:"shake what ya momma gave ya",hint:"moe ya bum"},
       {question:"dock keys tile",answer:"doggy style",hint:"ruff ruff"},
       {question:"aisle hike peg bus hike an hot done high",answer:"i like big butts and i cannot lie",hint:"can’t deny"},
       {question:"hue no hut the hays hay up out pick ands",answer:"you know what they say about big hands",hint:"large fingers"},
       {question:"hep pay ant ding",answer:"happy ending",hint:"joyous finale"},
       {question:"my grope bean his",answer:"micro penis",hint:"mini sausage"},
       {question:"try eave fin",answer:"dry heaving",hint:"no vom"},
       {question:"sec shoe holed inch in",answer:"sexual tension",hint:"tightrope"},
       {question:"pet oaf vial",answer:"pedophile",hint:"creep"},
       {question:"vole fur rental new did he",answer:"full frontal nudity",hint:"forward flashing"},
       {question:"sir gums his shin",answer:"circumcision",hint:"precise cut"},
       {question:"boo buzz wet",answer:"boob sweat",hint:"hot cleavage"},
       {question:"boat deke hall",answer:"booty call",hint:"that late text"},
       {question:"app heed rail",answer:"happy trail",hint:"hairy path"},
       {question:"nog tup",answer:"knocked up",hint:"preggo"},
       {question:"loaf fan dulls",answer:"love handles",hint:"well equipped"},
       {question:"loose eeyore fur chin knit he",answer:"lose your virginity",hint:"cherry on top"},
       {question:"slaw bees egg guns",answer:"sloppy seconds",hint:"silver medal"},
       {question:"mass tear bay gin",answer:"masturbation",hint:"self gratification"},
       {question:"wed he sured gone test",answer:"wet t shirt contest",hint:"see through"},
       {question:"sick shoe well lint hair gores",answer:"sexual intercourse",hint:"breeding"},
       {question:"wiz keyed hick",answer:"whiskey dick",hint:"floppy fish"},
       {question:"hoe more rag cur",answer:"homewrecker",hint:"moes burrito"},
       {question:"sum hag tad as",answer:"smack that ass",hint:"booty bop"},
       {question:"kid hang mite dig wed",answer:"getting my dick wet",hint:"underwater"},
       {question:"filet afford conned dumb",answer:"flavored condom",hint:"sweet safety"},
       {question:"hay read hose",answer:"hairy toes",hint:"feet fur"},
       {question:"gin hid all owe arts",answer:"genital warts",hint:"private pimples"},
       {question:"sell fur fogs",answer:"silver fox",hint:"gramps"},
       {question:"mourn ink have derp hill",answer:"morning after pill",hint:"safe not sorry"},
       {question:"bird they’s eggs",answer:"birthday sex",hint:"private present"},
       {question:"town nun doored he ",answer:"down and dirty",hint:"not up or clean"},
       {question:"sighed jig",answer:"side chick",hint:"hidden honey"},
       {question:"her ate it tar",answer:"rated R",hint:"says the pirate"},
       {question:"as seed inks ease on",answer:"ass eating season",hint:"periodic appetite"},
       {question:"less sum ache pay bays",answer:"lets make babies",hint:"reproduction"},
       {question:"hunk lie cohorts",answer:"hung like a horse",hint:"big baggage"},
       {question:"mean hut may inn",answer:"minute man",hint:"quick burst"},
       {question:"moth air hide lie who’ve ugg",answer:"mother id like to fuck",hint:"hi mom"},
       {question:"tad die dull hike dew fog",answer:"dad id like to fuck",hint:"hi pops"},
       {question:"won hint up ink doing thus tank",answer:"one in the pink two in the stink",hint:"versatile fingers"},
       {question:"bop ink dutch hairy",answer:"popping the cherry",hint:"first timer"},
       {question:"me ugh a leaf huh",answer:"mia khalifa",hint:"pornhub"},{question:"range imp owner",answer:"raging boner",hint:"very erect"},
       {question:"bus seal hick king",answer:"pussy licking",hint:"cat tasting"}
]    
module.exports={blueDeck,yellowDeck,redDeck,mixDeck};

//’
//'


